We, Seino!
Super Tough Strong Energy! Positively Exciting Soul from Nagoya Team Shaqi
Murasaki Purple kakko kari Ogura Yuzuki and
Ujina Michiko's Starlust
From Iginari Tohokusan! I'm Rine Kitami!
Yay!
Please join Rineko!
So this time, we two will send you this project!
Let's make baked sweet potatoes with purple sweet potatoes from OGURUZUKI and Hitomi Rine!
I know this is a bit sudden, but...
We're in charge of the team shirt and the purple color of Hitomirine, so we're going to make a baked sweet potato with purple sweet potatoes.
So, speaking of purple, let's make purple sweet potatoes.
Let's make purple sweet potatoes!
Do you often make yaki-imo? Do you ever make them?
I don't.
Of course you don't.
Do you have an image of making yaki-imo with fallen leaves?
Like a bonfire.
Have you ever done that?
No, I haven't.
Have you?
Probably not.
I heard that it's easy to make baked sweet potatoes.
I'd like to make it as soon as possible.
There seems to be a toaster in the studio.
They're going to make it in the toaster.
I can't imagine it at all!
We have a magnificent potato right here.
You like potatoes?
I love them.
Oh! I'm going to make a baked sweet potato with this.
Yay!
Okay, let's get started, but first, let's wash our hands. Important!
Let's wash our hands.
Mizuki washing hands scene.
I'll be there often.
I wonder how she usually washes her hands.
I usually do it like this, like this, like this.
Is that the type of person you are?
I'm pretty good at it.
That's new.
How do you like it?
You do it like that. That's good.
You're pretty good at keeping your hands out of the crevice. Yes, it is.
Okay, perfect. We're all set.
So, now that we've washed our hands, let's wash the limo.
Yes, please.
It's so purple. Wow!
It's purple. Yes, it is.
Isn't it amazing? This purple.
You should wash it with a lot of water.
And then?
And then, you soak this one in water, too.
What is this?
How do we do it?
As much as possible, because the water is dissolved here.
That's what I'm talking about.
My favorite uncle.
Do you think it'll go viral? Maybe it'll go viral.
It could go viral.
Is this really the right way to do it? I don't know if this is the right way to do it.
It sticks out.
These are the handles.
But...
It looks good.
It looks like this.
Wrap it with aluminum foil.
It's a little more.
A little more?
OK.
Aluminum foil comes in different colors, right? I wonder which is which.
Let's see.
Let's say it once.
Which is the inside?
Should I say it with my true feelings, or should I just go with it?
What do you mean? Let's be real.
I like the way you really feel. Can I take a look?
So, you want to wrap it up like this?
Okay, okay, I've decided.
Ready.
Wow, I didn't get it right.
Okay, this way.
Even if it's not the same, if we both say, yes, yes, this way, then yes.
We'll be one step out.
One step too far out? This is too big.
Let's do it this way.
Oh, sure.
Yes, it's right.
Is it right?
He's trying to do something that wasn't even discussed at all.
Oh, that's good. It might be perfect.
It's definitely wrapped up in a string like this.
Oh, yeah!
Yay.
Now all that's left is to ding it up.
Just put it in.
Open it. Here you go. Put it in.
Soy milk. Oh, it fits perfectly.
Isn't it great? It's huge.
Big,
An! Oh!
Why? Go!
15 minutes.
Hold on. Turn over and bake for 15 minutes.
Bake one eye first for 15 minutes.
So, while the potatoes are baking, I'd like to do a little purple talk.
Yay!
How did you decide on the color of your toke sans-chan in the first place? Each.
The staff says, "This is it. This is yours. And then the staff said, "This is it.
That's what they told us at the meeting.
We didn't know anything about it, and they just called us in one by one.
They called us in one by one?
They said, "You don't know anything.
That's funny!
We were already decided on our own,
While we were free-diving at the mall,
We weren't told anything about doing anything,
Suddenly, the chief manager came up on stage,
He told us that he was going to announce our image color,
He told me that he was going to announce our image color, and he did it in front of everyone,
And then he announced it in front of everyone.
What did you think?
You mean they said purple?
I don't know, I just thought it was...
What color did you like?
I liked pink.
Oh, pink, yes.
Yes, pink.
But also because of the character,
I was thinking yellow or purple,
I really liked Tagagi,
So I thought purple would be good,
I was so happy that it was purple.
Well, Rineko, how did you like it?
I don't know, I don't really like purple,
I don't really like purple,
I didn't dislike it, but it didn't have to be purple.
It was more like...something,
I liked blue and red, and at the time, I really liked those kinds of clear colors,
I was hoping for that kind of color,
Purple, huh?
I didn't think it was good or bad.
I just thought, "Hmmm...
I was like, "Hmmm.
I see. So that's how you decided.
That's very interesting.
But at first, Karen and the others are in pink, right?
We said we wanted light blue and pink,
Then they decided to go with pink.
So there were two light blue ones?
No, and Miyu is the opposite,
Not light blue.
Not light blue, but some kind of yellowish green?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But then it changed to light blue,
My memory is a little hazy,
I think it's been changed since it was announced.
Oh, I see.
What?
I don't remember much.
It has changed.
You didn't show much color at first.
Oh, that's right. That's right.
I see.
In the beginning, we just decided on a solid color,
It's true that there is an image of a number.
That's the way we felt about it,
That's how we felt,
Maybe you don't know that fact either,
You may not know that,
It's a very rare world, isn't it?
There were times when it was like that.
Hmm.
What about purple?
Yes, it is.
What kind of image do you have of it?
Well, purple in the group.
Uh, purple in the group?
What do you think?
Well, it's something, in my opinion,
Yes.
I don't think you should say too much,
In terms of cuestión,
Well, then, Accent.
I think it's a little bit..,
I mean, it's a bit of a stretch, but it's a little bit of a stretch,
I see the same affiliate,
I'm sure there are some of them.
I'll give you the метa4 word,
Teka-chan and company catty- purple,
I guess it's the story factor,
I don't know.
Bright, kind of a gruop.
I had an image of brightness and doing a lot of weird things,
I had an image of her as bright and doing lots of strange things.
But I thought it would be Koo-chan, or was it so?
Then I thought to myself, "Well, there's first purple and lavender purple," and I thought to myself, "I'm not going to wear it.
I thought I would wear it straight away, but I decided to go with eggplant purple.
And from A-chan, I existed in lavender raffia staples.
I don't know which one it is, but I'm not going to eat it!
but it looks so beautiful, you must have lavender, like a half eggplant, but if I knew, I'd say it's an eggplant
I'm half-Japanese, but I'm not the strongest half.
Julia's definitely a lavender girl, too... but purple makes me do weird things.
That's what I thought.
When I became purple, I thought, "I'm going to do weird things from now on.
I didn't have this image of purple as this kind of character.
But there are yellow and pink.
I think the color of purple is like the color of a performance.
I had an image of purple as a very bewitching color, so maybe it's the opposite of what I had in mind.
It's a curious color, and I think it's cool that each of you has your own unique style of live performance.
I think they all have something wonderful and cool about them in their live performances, but in everyday life, when they're just talking, people around me have the image that they're being teased.
I wanted to be Reni-chan Takagi, so I was happy to see that, but in a good way, what I thought was changing.
I thought purple was a color with a lot of room for growth.
I followed you. Will you follow me in Lusby?
Can you follow me as a half?
Of all the colors, that one has the most potential.
It has the most potential... but it can be funny or noble...
But when I see Precure and other things like that, the image of purple is more like a dependable older lady character.
I thought so myself. That's true.
Really? That's a big discovery.
I thought so. I thought so. I thought so.
That's right... that's why... that's why... that's why... that's why...
That's right, so maybe I was really influenced by the image of the purple man I saw back then.
Maybe I'm influenced by the image of the purple person I was watching at the time.
That's true.
I have a strong image of Yuzuki's purple.
Strong?
It's like purple is a big deal.
I'm glad to hear that, because she's proud of purple.
Purple's a nice color, isn't it?
Yes, it's cute.
But isn't purple pretty in an outfit?
If you make it darker, it can be cool.
It's a little strong.
But if you lighten it, it can be cute.
That's pretty good.
I think it's a color that can be dyed in various ways.
We will live as purple with pride in our hearts.
We will live as purple with pride in our hearts, so please give us your support!
Please support us!
Tomorrow, I'd like to continue this story a little bit.
I hope I can tell you more about it tomorrow.
And what happens to the sweet potatoes?
Yes, I'm anxious about it!
Please look forward to what will happen to the purple sweet potatoes!
So, that's it...
So far, I've been with Guruzuki of Team Shachi and
and Kitami Kine from Suddenly Tohoku!
Bye bye!